(Silence; Operating Room Area)
=Stand Up for Love=
=Episode 9=
Lulu.
Mom.
Haotian and I are already married.
Why do you still refuse to accept him?
Signing a prenuptial agreement,
do you know how hurtful it is?
He always feels like he doesn't
belong in this family.
Like he'll never have your approval.
It's affecting our relationship.
Don't you understand?
Lulu.
If you want to keep Zhang Haotian
by your side,
this agreement must stay with me.
Trust me.
I would never hurt you.
Give me the password.
No.
Tell me!
I won't say it twice.
(Haotian is starting to get restless.)
(I need to put him in his place.)
(That woman named Zhao Ke...)
(Maybe she can be useful.)
Ms. Su.
Zhao Ke's file.
(Background Check: Zhao Ke)
Ms. Su.
Ms. Su?
(Background Check: Zhao Ke)
How strange.
When I look at her,
I feel something I can't quite explain.
(Unknown Number)
What brings you here?
Are you sure you want to keep
going with this?
Zhang Haotian believes I'm Zhao Ke.
My nightclub persona played
a huge part in that.
If I suddenly quit now,
he'll get suspicious.
I've set a trap specifically
for Zhang Haotian.
Once he falls in, he won't be able
to escape.
So don't force yourself
to do something you don't want to do.
But
I don't want to just wait here.
My other kidney is with Su Qinglan.
I want to find a way to get close
to her.
And...
Su Qinglan is a successful
businesswoman.
She must know Zhang Haotian's
true nature.
If she knew the truth and still
let her daughter marry him,
she'd never side with an outsider.
If things go wrong,
the moment you contact her,
Zhang Haotian will find out.
Then we'll really be in trouble.
(Unknown Number)
Hold on, I need to take this call.
Hello?
Hi.
This is Su Qinglan.
Ms. Su?
What can I do for you?
When are you available?
I'd like to meet and talk.
I work nights.
I'm free during the day.
Alright. I'll let you know the time
and place.
It was Su Qinglan.
She suddenly asked to meet with me.
It's her?
(Lin Lulu definitely didn't
get the agreement.)
(Otherwise, given her personality,)
(she would've called me by now.)
Baby.
Why are you crying, baby?
I'm sorry.
I couldn't get the agreement back.
It's okay.
Whether you got the agreement or not,
I'm still your husband.
I'll always be the man who loves you
most in this life.
(If I can't get the agreement back,)
(then I'll have to get rid
of Su Qinglan sooner than planned.)
Baby,
I'm a little tired today.
I'll get some rest first, okay?
Honey?
(All-Star Party Space)
Zhao Ke.
I'm giving you a chance
to earn my forgiveness.
No.
I don't need your forgiveness.
Name your price.
No amount of money will make me do it.
Zhao Ke.
I've already lowered myself
by coming to you.
And you still don't know
what's good for you?
Don't make me have someone
drag you there.
You don't seem to understand.
Did you really think the videos
of Zhang Haotian and me
only showed what happened at the mall?
No.
There's footage in the car.
And there's footage here too.
I think you're just trying to drive
a wedge between me and my husband.
Shut up!
If you have that much free time,
come on, let's go upstairs
and check the cameras.
Let's see what your precious husband
is really like.
Zhao Ke, I'll make you pay
for these lies!
I won't let you off.
Are you sure you want to increase
the dosage for Su Qinglan?
I've had enough of Lin Lulu.
I can't wait any longer. Besides...
Su Qinglan must be investigating me
behind my back.
She can't be left alive.
I understand. It's just that...
You're more experienced
in this area than I am.
Yet you're still worried?
I can't explain it.
I just have a bad feeling about this.
Just sit back and wait.
You'll enjoy
your wealth and luxury soon.
Haotian.
Lulu.
You were gone first thing this morning.
Where did you go?
Were you with another woman?
Answer me!
Zhang Haotian. Answer me!
I went to the office to handle
some things.
There is no other woman.
I don't believe you.
Give me your phone.
Let me check your phone.
What's wrong, Lulu?
Zhang Haotian,
who is this?
Who's your "best love"?
I knew it. You have someone else.
(My Best Love)
Who is it? Who?
(Pinned; Be With U
This Year, Next Year, Every Year)
Me?
I...
My contact name...
When did you change it?
After you found out about Zhao Ke
and me.
Lulu, lately,
a lot of things have happened
that hurt you.
Let me take you somewhere to relax.
(Taking you away to clear your mind)
(is just to buy me enough time
to make my move)
(and create an alibi.)
(Su Qinglan Calling)
Hello, Ms. Su.
Miss Zhao, I'm terribly sorry.
I'd like to change the time.
Of course. I'll work around
your schedule.
(Su Qinglan
Call in Progress)
Ms. Su?
(Su Qinglan
Call Ended)
Ms. Su?
Hello?
911?
(Crocodile Tears)
♪Listen, the wind chimes softly whisper♪
♪I should forget you♪
♪But I have the will,
yet not the strength♪
♪To carry on♪
♪The scenery you once longed to see♪
♪You no longer have the strength♪
♪You want me to go there for you♪
♪I look up and see a hollow sky♪
♪Your freedom♪
♪Has become my cage♪
♪My hand brushes over your smile
in the photograph♪
♪This glass of wine is filled
with sorrow♪
♪I look up at the beautiful night sky♪
♪You told me♪
♪I would shine like a star♪
♪But you forgot to teach me♪
♪How to live without you♪
♪I look up♪
♪The starry sky♪
♪So hazy and blurred♪